[MUSIC PLAYING]
[詳細 [音楽再生]
Well, good news.
さて、良い知らせです。
You made it to the end of this training.
あなたはこのトレーニングの最後まで辿り着きました。 このトレーニングは終了です。
I wanted to just spend a couple of minutes pointing out
私はただ、2分ほどかけて 数分かけて指摘したいと思います。
some additional resources that will be helpful to you
いくつかの追加資料 を紹介したいと思います。
as you continue to work with Gallery.
ギャラリーでの作業を継続する上で ギャラリーで作業する際に役立ちます。
I highly recommend checking out the Brightcove Support
ぜひ ブライトコーブ サポートをご覧ください。
Site located at support.brightcove.com.
サイトは support.brightcove.com にあります。
Let's take a quick look at the support site.
サポート サイトを簡単に見てみましょう。 サポートサイトを見てみましょう。
The Support Site is organized into a series of micro-sites
サポートサイトは 一連のマイクロサイトとして構成されています。
for each product or focus area.
のように、製品別・分野別に構成されています。
Let's click on the gallery logo to go
ギャラリーロゴをクリックすると
to the Gallery Documentation.
をクリックするとギャラリードキュメントが表示されます。
The Gallery Home Page has all the links you'll need.
ギャラリーのホームページには 必要なリンクがあります。
If you're new to Gallery, the Getting Started link
Galleryを初めてご利用になる場合。 入門のリンク
will take you to a page with some Getting Started resources.
をクリックすると 入門のページがあります。
There are links to the Step by Step Documents,
このページには ステップバイステップのドキュメントへのリンクがあります。
Product Overview information on the Templates.
製品概要情報 テンプレートにあります。
It links to the online Training that's available.
オンライントレーニングにリンクしています。 トレーニングにリンクしています。
The left navigation could be used
左側のナビゲーション を使うことができます。
to browse the site categories.
をクリックすると、サイトのカテゴリが表示されます。
We try to use the categories to group topics by subject.
私たちは、カテゴリを利用して を使っています。
We just saw the Getting Started section.
今、入門編を見ました。 セクションを見ました。
The Experiences section has documents
エクスペリエンス にはドキュメントがあります。
organized by experience type.
のように、体験の種類ごとに整理されています。
The Training section has links to online training courses
トレーニング」セクションには オンライン・トレーニング・コースへのリンクがあります。
and training videos.
とトレーニングビデオへのリンクがあります。
Finally, the Release Notes section
最後に、「リリース ノートのセクション
is where you can read about all the product updates.
には、製品のアップデート情報が掲載されています。 をご覧ください。
All of the support pages will have a search
すべてのサポート 検索ができます。
field at the top of the page.
のフィールドがページ上部にあります。
If you know what you're looking for, just search for it.
何を探しているのかわかっているのなら 検索してください。
I want to learn more about Templates,
もっと詳しく知りたい テンプレートについて
so that's what I'll search for.
ということで、それを検索してみます。
The Results page should do a pretty good job of returning
結果ページでは を返してくれるはずです。
what you're looking for.
といった具合です。
All search results from the Gallery Site
すべての検索結果 ギャラリーサイトからの検索結果
will display under This Site tab.
の下に表示されます。 このサイト]タブに表示されます。
You can also click on the All Brightcove Documentation tab
また、[All] をクリックすることもできます。 Brightcove ドキュメント] タブをクリックすることもできます。
to see a list of search results across all the support sites.
をクリックすると、すべてのサポート サイトの検索結果のリストが表示されます。 をクリックすると、すべてのサポート サイトの検索結果の一覧が表示されます。
The page header has links to contact Brightcove Support
ページ ヘッダには、以下へのリンクがあります。 ブライトコーブ サポートに連絡する
and for viewing the System Status page.
および システム ステータス ページを表示するためのリンクがあります。
Thank you for taking the time to watch this training.
本トレーニングをご覧いただき、ありがとうございました。 このトレーニングをご覧いただきありがとうございます。
If you have any questions on the content
内容に関して ご質問等ございましたら
or suggestions for improvement, feel free to email us
また、改善点などございましたら お気軽にメールしてください。
at training@brightcove.com.
にて、training@brightcove.com。